

# IRYNA SKARAIEVA

# **Front-End Developer**

I'm a Front-End Developer transitioning into IT after many years of working in education. My teaching experience has equipped me with strong analytical skills, problem-solving abilities, and teamwork capabilities. With a foundation in JavaScript, React and HTML/CSS, I focus on crafting functional, visually appealing web applications to enhance user experiences.

Proposals for cooperation with technologies that need to be studied are welcome!

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

+421919495444

Trnava, Slovak Republic

## LINKS TO OTHER RESOURCES

<u>Portfolio</u> WhatsApp Telegram

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Facebook</u> <u>GitHub</u>

#### **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

**JavaScript** 

**SCSS** 

React

Next.js

**Figma** 

Bulma

**Tailwind CSS** 

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Content Manager**

Freelance, Vinnytsya, UA | Feb 2016 - May 2017

- · Researched and edited photos and product descriptions to optimize content for online stores.
- · Managed content updates, gaining experience in web content structuring and user experience.

### **Teacher of Physics and Astronomy**

Medical College, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2014 - Aug 2015 Secondary School, Odesa, UA | Sep 2007 - Sep 2012

- · Created educational materials (presentations, interactive content), building skills in design and multimedia.
- $\cdot$  Managed large amounts of information, developed instructional documentation.
- · Supervised student groups.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Ukrainian C2

Russian C2

English B1

Slovak B1

# **DRIVING LICENSE**

В

## Accountant

T&T, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2013 - Mar 2013

- · Processed financial transactions and records, requiring data accuracy and attention to detail.
- · Handled large datasets for reporting, building analytical thinking relevant in software development.
- $\cdot$  Adapted to new software, showing flexibility and a quick learning curve for new tools.

#### **EDUCATION**

### The Faculty of Physics and Mathematics

Teacher of Physics, Computer Science and Life Safety Basics

Master's degree Sep 2002 — June 2007

South Ukrainian National Pedagogical University named after K. D. Ushynsky